

Profile

I am an Interior Designer ,with experience of more than 2 years ,based in New Delhi. I wish to seek this opportunity in the organisation to boost my career along with acomplishing the organisational goals as well as benefit to the

Language

English

Hind

My Skills

Creativity

Team Work

Communication

Dedication

Sakshi Mittal

INTERIOR DESIGNER

Phone 9873492620

E-Mail

sakshimittal1255@gmail.com

Address

259, Bhera Enclave,Paschim Vihar, New Delhi - 110087

Education

Master Diploma in Interior & Architecture Design (MDIAD)

IVS School Of Design 2017-2019

Masters in Commerce (M.Com)

Indira Gandhi National Open University 2017-2019

Bachelors in Commerce (B.Com)

Delhi University, Bharati College 2014-2017

Software Skills

Autocad

Photoshop

Google Sketchup

3ds Max

MS Office Suite



Work Experience

Interior Author, Ashok Vihar

January 2021-April 2021 (Internship)

Interior Author, Ashok Vihar

April 2021-August 2023

- Worked on 30+ Residential within the span of 2 years
- Designing projects on the basis of client requirements and concepts through working drawings and communicating the drawings to labours for execution.
- Site handling and finishing the projects within a particular time period